Guide to the Grigori Mints Papers SC1225
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Subject files
  - Logic and Computer Science, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - The Journal of Symbolic Logic, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Automated Reasoning with Analytic Tableaux and Related Methods, 1997 May. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Logic Programming and Automated Response, 1992 Jul. (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Logic Colloquium, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Iterated Inductive Definitions and Subsystems of Analysis: Recent Proof-Theoretical Studies, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Logic Colloquium, 1972-73 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Proof Theory: An Introduction, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Logic, Methodology and Philosophy of Science VII, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Kreiseliana Abound and Around Georg Kreisel, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Pillars of Computer Science: Essays Dedicated to Boris (Boaz) Trakhtenbrot on the Occasion of His 85th Birthday, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Baltic Computer Science, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Computational Logic and Proof Theory, 1993 Aug. (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - COLOG-88, 1988 Dec. (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Logic for Programming, Artificial Intelligence, and Reasoning, 2006 Nov. (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Correct Reasoning: Essays on Logic-Based AI in Honor of Vladmir Lifschitz, 2012 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Fields of Logic and Computation: Essays Dedicated to Yuri Gurevich on the Occasion of His 70th Birthday, 2010 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Computer Science - Theory and Applications, 2006 Jun. (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Locial Foundations of Computer Science, 1997 Jul. (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Logic Colloquium, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Logic, Language, Information and Computation, 2011 May. (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Reflections on the Foundations of Mathematics, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - European Summer Meeting for the Association for Symbolic Logic, 1996 Jul 9-15 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Bulletin of the American Mathematical Society, 1997 Apr. (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - PYC, undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - PYC 0-T, undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - PYC H, undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - PYC ^M, undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - PYC E-K, undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - A, undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - R, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - RUS AbB, undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Non-recursive functions, knots "with thick ropes" and self-clenching "thick" hyperspheres, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - A Characterization Theorem for Geometric Logic, 12/8/2009 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - OE3OP, undated (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - About Sergei Yu Maslov, undated (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - The Variety of Logical Hylomorphism, undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - A Finite Model Theorem for the Propositional u-Calculus, undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Results on the Propositional u-Calculus, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - A Buchholz Rule for Modal fixed Point Logics, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - PhML, 2014 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Mathematics 21th Century PDMI 70th Anniversary, 2010 Sep. 13-18 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Kant's Theory of Judgment, 4/23/2009 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Epsilon Substitution for Predicate Logic, undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - On Mints' Reduction for ccc-Calculus, undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Provable Isomorphisms of Types, undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Normal Forms and Cut-Free Proofs as Natural Transformations, undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - On Gentzen's First Consistency Proof for Arithmetic, 6/13/2012 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - On Gentzen's First Consistency Proof for Arithmetic (Revised), 3/10/2013 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Structural Polymorphism, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Functional Polymorphism, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Proof search in multi-succeedent sequent calculi for intuitionistic logic, undated (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Proof Theory and Category Theory, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Proof Theory and Category Theory, 2013 Jul. 24-27 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Catbeam1, 7/13/2013 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - A Reconstruction of Aristotle's Modal Syllogistic, 9/9/2005 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - International Who's Who of Intellectuals, undated (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Sudoku, undated (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - What is Truth?, 4/4/2012 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Register Machines, undated (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - What is Truth, Spring 2012 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Manin, Mosogsky, etc., undated (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - MT2009 Dec. Theories (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Sasha, 2008-2009 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Comment tracer des diagrammes commutatifs?, 6/24/2003 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Kripke Models, undated (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - A Short Introduction to Intuitionistic Logic, undated (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Rooted Frames, Partial Orders, undated (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Algebraic Models, undatred (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Topological Completeness, undated (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Epsilon Substitution for First- and Second-Order Predicate Logic, 4/29/2011 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Category Theory and Structural Proof Theory, 10/27/2009 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Introduction to Ergodic Theory, Winter 1995 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Comput., undated (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Academies, undated (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Students, 2009-2012 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Seminars, 2008-2009 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - LMH, 2008-2009 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Logteach, 2011-2013 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Kant, undated (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - ID, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Estonian AS, undated (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Constructivity, undated (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Number Theory, Winter 2007 (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - The Indeterminacy of Set-Theoretic Notions, undated (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Confer, undated (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - "What is Truth?" - Slides: Typos and other Observations, 11/30/2013 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - Cantor's Disorganization Method, undated (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Introducing Topoi, 10/18/2013 (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Second Order Arithmetic, undated (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - American Academy of Arts & Sciences, undated (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - Mathematics self-proves its own Consistency, undated (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - O-minimal Structures - Phil350B Decidable Theories, Autumn 2013 (Box 40, Folder 57)
  - Grobner Bases, 10/21/2013 (Box 40, Folder 58)
  - Intuitionistic Hybrid Logic, 4/1/2005 (Box 40, Folder 59)
  - Intuitionistic Decision ProceduresGesamtersetzungen in Ackermanns Dissertation, 10/8/2003 (Box 40, Folder 60)
  - Univalent Foundations and the Structure Identity Principle, 1/8/2013 (Box 40, Folder 61)
  - Amalgation and Interpolation in Normal Modal Logics, undated (Box 40, Folder 62)
  - Two Examples of Cut-Elimination for Non-classical Logics, 12/13/2013 (Box 40, Folder 63)
  - Latex, undated (Box 40, Folder 64)
  - Submitted, undated (Box 40, Folder 65)
  - Logic Seminar, 2010 (Box 40, Folder 66)
  - Additive Number Theory, 2/7/2007 (Box 40, Folder 67)
  - Strong Normalisation Theorem, undated (Box 40, Folder 68)
  - Work of A.A. Markov on Stepwise Semantics of Constructive Mathematics, undated (Box 40, Folder 69)
  - Memorandum of Agreement, undated (Box 40, Folder 70)
  - Cut-elimination for the first order of e-calculus, 10/27/1992 (Box 40, Folder 71)
  - Ordinals from Above and Below, Part II, 1/25/2011 (Box 40, Folder 72)
  - PhML-14, undated (Box 40, Folder 73)
  - Invariants, undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - QBF, undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Decomposing Two-Dimensional Permutations: A Three Layer Cryptoticon is Universal, 8/27/2012 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Carolyn, undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Kaht, undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Documents, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Proof T4, 2010-2011 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Intuitionistic Dual-intuistionistic Nets, 2009 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - From Deep Inference to Proof Nets via Cut Elimination, 2009 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Eigenvalues, bracketing and the decidability of positive minimal intuitionistic logic, undated (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Transfinite Progressions: A Second Look at Completeness, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Functional Interpretations of Classical Systems, undated (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Godel incompleteness theorems and the limits of their applicability., 2010 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Eskolemization in Intuitionistic Logic, 2009 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Tableaux and Hypersequents for Justification Logics, 2011 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Cut Elimination for Shallow Modal Logics, 2011 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Analytic Cut in Modal Logic: the System B, 2011 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Epsilon Substitution for First and Second Order Predicate Logic, 4/29/2011 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Proof TH, 2010-2011 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Philosophy, Mathematics, Linguistics: Aspects of Interaction, 22-25 May, 2012 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - The Calculus Can Be Put to Work as Mathematics, not Formalism!, 10/30/2012 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Iterating Semantic Automata, 9/3/2012 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Common Law Reasoning, undated (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Modal Logic and Philosophy, 2007 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Epsilon of Fprints, undated (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Category Theory and Structured Proof Theory, 11/9/2009 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Equational/Categorical Axiomatizations of Primitive Recursive Functions and Functionals, 11/10/2010 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Strong Normalization with Permutative Conversions, 11/16/2007 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Epsilon Substitution for ID1, 5/23/2009 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Additive Number Theory, 1/10/2007 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Fitch's Paradox of Knowability, 4/4/2004 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - First Steps in Modal Logic, 12/4/2007 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Catastrophic Second Step of Hilbert's Program, 8/24/2012 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Several Interesting Problems from Applied Logic, 1/29/2013 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Generalized Godel, Rosser, and Henkin Sentences, undated (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Epsilon Substitution for Predicate Logic, 8/22/2010 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Semantic Construction of Intuitionistic Logic, undated (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - There is no 16-Clue Sudoku: Solving the Sudoku Minimum Number of Clues Problem, 1/1/2012 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Kolmogorov Complexity of Categories, 1/8/2013 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Justification of Tertium Non Datur Within Hilbert's Consistency Theory, undated (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Extension of Epsilon Substituition Method to ID1, 6/22/2007 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Recursively Mahlo Ordinals and Inductive Definitions, undated (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - General Interest Topics in Mathematical Logic, 11/18/2010 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Non-Deterministic Epsilon Substituion Method for PA and ID1, 7/13/2011 (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Annotated Bibliography on Decidability in Non-Clasical Systems, undated (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - Craig's Interpolation Theorem for the Intuitionistic Logic and its Extensions - A Semantical Approach, undated (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - Ordinals: Pohlers, Proof Theory, 1989-1994 (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - Renormalization and Computation, 10/20/2009 (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - Summary of Presentaions Given at the Stanford Logic Seminar, 2007-2008 (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - Simplified Strong Normalization Proof for Logic With Existence, 6/6/1997 (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - Non-Deterministic Epsilon Substituion Method for ID1: Effective Proof, 1/20/2012 (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - Idempotents in Compact Semigroups and Ramsey Theory, undated (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Report on Non-Deterministic Epsilopn Substitution for ID1: Effective Proof, 2/5/2012 (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - The Theory ID1, undated (Box 41, Folder 54)
  - Avron Hypersequent Calculus for Godal-Dummet Logic, 8/24/2008 (Box 41, Folder 55)
  - Review of Mathematical Logic, undated (Box 41, Folder 56)
  - A Survey of Decidability Results in Non-Classical Logics, 8/16/2011 (Box 41, Folder 57)
  - Derivability of Modal Formulas Containing Only Positive Occurances of Quantifiers, 8/9/2011 (Box 41, Folder 58)
  - Generalized Kripke Forms, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 59)
  - CST, undated (Box 41, Folder 60)
  - Notices of the American Mathematical Society, 2014 Mar. (Box 41, Folder 61)
  - Notes on Constructive Negation, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 62)
  - No Plagiarism Here, undated (Box 41, Folder 63)
  - Constructive Set Theory, 1975 Sep. (Box 41, Folder 64)
  - PhML, 2014 (Box 41, Folder 65)
  - Proceedings of the Estonian Academy of Sciences, 2014 (Box 41, Folder 66)
  - Cut Elimination for tge Logic of Transivity and Density, 5/6/2013 (Box 41, Folder 67)
  - Compositional Semantics vs Arbitrary Syntax, 9/27/2013 (Box 41, Folder 68)
  - Semialgebraic and Subanalytic Geometry, 3/2/2000 (Box 41, Folder 69)
  - An introduction to o-minimal structures, 9/3/1999 (Box 41, Folder 70)
  - Pfaffian Sets and O-minimality, 2012 (Box 41, Folder 71)
  - Exponential Complexity of Satisfiability Testing for Linear-Size Boolean Formulas, 2013 (Box 41, Folder 72)
  - Satisfiability Certificates Verifiable in Subexponential Time, 2011 (Box 41, Folder 73)
  - A deterministic (2-2(k+1))^n algorithm for k-SAT based on local search, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 74)
  - Clause Shortening Combined with Pruning Yields a New Upper Bound for Deterministic SAT Algorithms, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 75)
  - MAX-SAT for Formulas with Constant Clause Density Can Be Solved Faster Than in O(2^n) Time, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 76)
  - Expressive Power and Data Complexity of Nonrecursive Query Languages for Lists and Trees, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 77)
  - On Moderately Exponential Time for SAT, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 78)
  - Simple Proof of Strong Normalization, 6/20/2012 (Box 41, Folder 79)
  - A Simple Strong Normalization Proof with Existence and Disjunction, 12/11/2010 (Box 41, Folder 80)
  - Simplified Strong Normalization Proof for Logic With Existence, 11/3/1998 (Box 41, Folder 81)
  - A Simple Strong Normalization Proof with Existence and Disjunction, 8/23/2008 (Box 41, Folder 82)
  - Dynamic Logics of Dynamical Systems, undated (Box 41, Folder 83)
  - Proof Search in Multi-Succedent Sequent Calculi for Intuitionistic Logic, 4/1/2014 (Box 41, Folder 84)
  - Several Interesting Problems from Applied Logic, 2014 Apr. (Box 41, Folder 85)
  - Notices of the American Mathematical Society, 2014 Jan. (Box 41, Folder 86)
  - A Lower Bound for Intuitionistic Logic, 1/25/2007 (Box 41, Folder 87)
  - Implicit Definition and the Epistemology of Mathematics, undated (Box 41, Folder 88)
  - Aristotle's Modal Proof Theory, 2014 Mar. 4-6 (Box 41, Folder 89)
  - Offprint from Oxford Studies in Ancient Philosophy, Summer 2012 (Box 41, Folder 90)
- Additional papers, Accession ARCH-2015-139
  - Grigori Mints memorial materials, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A Short Introduction to Modal Logic, by Grigori Mints, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)